As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices We take in the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled
yeah yeah Here we are in between the sea
and the sky Ready now for adventure We're
itching to try Get ready to roam So all
aboard now we're said to go Set sail to
the ocean so deep Ready for a truly grand
adventure Well don't you think that sounds
really fun All this
excitement second to none
As we all travel across
the sea Raising our
voices we take In the beautiful blue world
Our spirits ready to go Everybody rejoices
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled
If there's something that I just won't ever
forget It's the way that I felt when our
journey was set Now I won't be scared As
long as I keep that
feeling there With that,
let us keep up the pace While
enjoying every trip from place to
place Our timid hearts get the
rhythm ingrained So let's keep going,
adventure awaits So many treasures
await So now let's raise our voices
in pride Laughing out when they are
found With all the riches in hand,
everybody rejoices Party on,
cause we stand tall and proud
Life is adventurous, be aware it's
dangerous Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
Is out to get you too?
No doubt about it.
I see.
We hide in this dark forest,
scared of zombies and.
All the other creatures here.
We can't head out to sea because
we'll be exposed to the sun.
With this body weakened the way it is.
It's hard to find the
will to keep on living.
Once, just once, before I die.
I want to walk under the sun
to feel it's warmed on my skin.
Just one.
One more time!
That's awful! How touching!
You've been through so much!
Such a gut-wrenching story!
But I'm not crying, got it? Jerk!
You won't make me cry!
Oh, come on, you big crybaby.
You're way too compassionate
about this kind of stuff.
Enough of this.
Hey, creepy grandpa!
Only ladies get to persuade people with
their tears show a little backbone will ya?
Oh boy
Well, you're in luck.
We're actually looking for
a guy that steals shadows
and I'm pretty sure he's the
one if he's coming after us!
Then that just makes things easier.
I'm gonna kick his ass and if
that saves you while we're at it.
It's fine by me Okay
Oh, that's very kind of you?
Thank you! Thank you!
You've given me new hope!
We can't thank you enough!
We're counting on you!
Yeah, Tremoria a new one!
What the hell?
The other victims, huh?
It's not polite to eavesdrop!
Oh, sorry about that, Mr.
Freaky Curly Eyebrows Guy!
That's a crappy way to apologize!
That's Dr.
Hotback's laugh for sure!
So is this the secret lab?
I sure hope it is!
Vice!
My work is almost finished!
At last!
Behold, Shinri!
This is a true work of art!
The work of a genius!
I hope this stupid thing blows
up and burns your face off.
Why would you even say that?!
Shandora, please.
You make me anxious with all those unnecessary
and frankly hateful remarks of yours.
I prepared a midnight snack for you.
Oh, wonderful.
What is it tonight?
I call it spaghetti soup.
Wait!
You're spilling soup all over the place!
Be careful!
I wish every last plate in the world...
Yes, yes, I know.
But considering your hatred for plates,
perhaps you should choose a better menu.
How about roast beef or turkey?
Maybe some pita bread or
some sort of sandwich.
You know, solid foods.
Did she really die in an accident
like that newspaper article said?
No, no, it's fine. I'll eat it.
It's too late now.
I'll lick it off the table.
What is that thing anyway?
It looks like a human body.
Though judging by those injuries,
he must be dead already.
He has a number on him too, just
like the zombies in the graveyard.
And Hogback said he was almost finished.
Well, I think that settles it.
What we're about to see here is
the creation of a new zombie.
And that means that Dr.
Hogback made all of the other undead
creatures on the island as well.
There's no other explanation.
Yeah, but even if he's a genius, it
can't be that easy to bring people back.
You saw it.
There were tons of those things.
You don't think he made all
of them himself, do you?
Regardless of what we think
we'll see for ourselves,
If there really is some kind of secret
to bringing the dead back to life.
Then this has gotta be it right?
Good evening.
What's the matter?
If you're going to stand there and
stare, you might as well go inside!
You three.
Why are you here?
Hey, that guy was... well.
I could have sworn it
was broke back there.
Yeah, I know.
But he wasn't a skeleton.
And maybe you fools,
he found us.
Indeed, now what did you say?
Didn't I tell?
Tell you never to peek
into my research room.
We didn't see anything.
Right, that thing, we swear.
I didn't see anything at all.
Really?
Really, it's the honest truth.
We certainly didn't see that
zombie you were making. Dumbass!
All right, fine then.
I'm sure you figured out some of my
secrets by now, but you're too late.
In but a few minutes, the
Night Hunt will begin.
The Night Hunt?
Woe and to those foolish enough
to wander this island after dark!
No intruder shall survive the Night Hunt!
You can't properly start the night hunt
if you're still buried now can you?
Now rise zombie soldiers.
No matter how many times you fall
you get back up and attack again.
That's what makes those
zombiees so terrifying!
Yeah, we know.
Don't be like that stop slacking off.
Get a grip on yourself zombies.
Now which one of you
wants to tell me who I am?
I know, the leader.
Our glorious leader, Absalom!
Leader, leader, leader, leader!
Bless the pink and girls.
Liener! Pervert! Pervert! Pervert!
Shut up!
Welcome back, Mr. Spirona. How are you?
Shut up, Kumasi!
Your voice is so deep, it's gross!
Just can it, okay?
My apologies.
Either be cute or get lost.
I won't have ugly things working for me.
Hair, Hair, Hair, Hair, Hair!
Hurry,
hurry up It's starting, it's starting
Time for the night hunt 12 o 'clock,
midnight Body up, Master Master
Moria It's time to get up, Master Me,
do it Right, here goes
Master Moria
Ah, I was having a bad dream.
Really?
Great, aren't those the best, Master?
Master Moria has been sleeping
since the night hunt four days ago.
Even so, that hasn't stopped us.
Knowing that you'd be
hungry when you awoke,
we have prepared a very special meal
that's sure to appease your appetite.
And they're a tough bunch.
Amazing fighters, too.
They're the pirates that brought
down the island of Eni's Lobby,
known as the Straw Hat Pirates.
Aren't you pleased?
Beast! Master!
Imagine what you could do with them!
Man, that sure came from out of nowhere.
It's really coming down, too.
Should we run for the mansion?
Hang on a sec. Huh?
I see something really big
by the mansion over there.
It looks like some kind
of mark. A mark? Hmm?
Hmm?
The rain's clearing the fog.
I see it.
Is that a flag? No.
I'm pretty sure that's a sail.
What?
Yes, you're right.
Hey, why are you still following us?
Right about what?
Like he said, what you see is
a sail of gigantic proportion.
It's so large that seeing the entire
thing at once is quite difficult.
You see, Thriller Bark is not
the island it appears to be.
Believe it or not, it's actually
the world's largest pirate ship.
The back of the mansion is
where you'll find the main mast.
It's also the home of Gecko Moria.
Now, zombie soldiers!
The zombie generals will lead the attack!
Let's finish off those pirates! March!
The rest of you will
find ways to corner and
overtake those among them
that fear the undead.
Show them no mercy.
Together we will crush them.
Now go, make me proud!
There's the bell.
The moment has arrived.
It's time to get serious.
If those pirates think they can escape
this place alive, they're gravely mistaken.
Are the preparations complete, my zombies?
In this dark realm are
the ghosts and ghouls.
This place we call Thriller Bar.
They are going to see nothing short
of a nightmare to end all nightmares.
Well, here we go.
To the ghost mansion.
What was that nonsense about
studying zombies, Hogback?
There's no hiding it now.
We know you're the one making
all the creatures on this island.
So out with the truth already.
Whoa easy there Nami.
Don't piss him off
Your accusations are meaningless
whether they're true or not,
but out of curiosity, what's your proof?
We read your assistant's obituary.
Victoria Shandora you died ten years ago?
You cretins!
How the hell did you know that?
My dear Change, samurai Ryuma,
throw them into the world of
darkness, never to return!
Wait!
Let's talk this over!
Sorry, doctor, but I'm afraid
it's too late for that now.
The night hunt has already begun, you see.
Oh my, upon closer inspection, you're
quite the lovely young lady, aren't you?
Beautiful!
That said, perhaps you would like
to show me your panty? Yeah, right.
I know that line.
This can't just It must be a coincidence.
This fellow is of a much better stock than
the zombies you've encountered thus far.
He is one of my zombie generals.
His body is quite special.
It harkens from the country
of Wano in the New World.
They call his sort a samurai,
and this one supposedly slayed a flying
dragon, at least according to the legend.
Stay back! Stay back!
Please don't hurt me!
Force! Force! Force! Force!
Force!
There's nowhere to run.
Shandora, if you would, my dear,
please open that door for me.
And if you have a moment,
I'd like a sandwich as well.
Wait, what happened?
I thought he was going to cut us.
Yeah, so did I.
He looked really scary just then.
Whatever, you guys.
Come on, let's get out of
here while we still can.
Look, the door is wide open.
Good point. Uh, right.
Run!
Splendid.
Fuss, fuss, fuss, fuss.
They say when a true master cuts you, you
can just walk away humming and smiling.
It's not until later that you
realize you've been struck down.
Three verse humming there are not
Hello nobody's there.
I'm going in hey give them a minute
It's locked
Hey, now it opens.
Yeah, since you smashed the lock
off, doesn't seem like anyone's here.
Hey!
Any monsters in here?
Get go, Moria!
Shouldn't there be a servant around here?
They've got to have tons of
them in a mansion this size.
And what's with the mess?
They have a fight in here or what?
They better not have heard Nami.
You're quite audacious
aren't you those who
know our master usually know to fear him?
Why is there a pig
sticking out of the wall?
Well that's great are these painting
zombies too that's certainly what it looks
like after All we've seen on this island
we should expect this sort of thing by now.
I'll only ask this once.
Where did you hide Nami?
Screaming like that isn't very ladylike.
A shame since you're so pretty.
You think so?
You're better off just staying
in your frame and smiling.
Now twist!
He broke my spirit half!
What is this guy's body made of, metal?
Okay, stop, stop, stop!
Who are you guys?
You're really on the same crew
as those cowards from before?
Yep!
Two-sword style. Nigiri! Nigiri?
What is that sushi? Gidisa!
Open wide!
I just picked ramen!
Wow, this island's like a party
everywhere you go! You! Metal!
Warp! Grr!
Grr!
Too bad!
If you hadn't tried to smash me, I
would have asked you to join my crew!
Now, Gum-Gum!
Monkey!
No!
Not fair, Rug!
that takes care of
that oh those three
friends of yours we fed
them bathed them and
gave them a warm bed to sleep in good news
right we're all friends like we're gonna
fall for that no I swear I'm not lying to
you why don't you go
see for yourself right
up those stairs go ahead
hold on something's
wrong here didn't you notice our chef is
missing huh he was just here a second ago
any of you zombie guys see where he went
they
must have nabbed
him and taken him away
while we weren't looking
goodbye Sanji rest
in peace that ain't cool no biggie it's
Sanji I'm sure he's
gonna be fine maybe but
I'm worried about the
other three if If the
zombies were able to
kidnap Sanji so easily,
I'm sure they're in a
lot of trouble right now.
You're not so strong.
The truth of the matter is you hardly
even put a dent in our numbers.
Oh?
You, on the other hand, just
lost one of your key fighters.
I wonder who's next.
At any rate, let's be careful and
try to stick together from now on.
Admit it, you're scared.
You don't stand a chance.
I suppose that we could threaten
him, but even if we did,
I doubt he would tell us where they are.
Fine, we'll just drag him with
us and use him as a guide.
Wado?
Yes, guide them.
Hey now, come on. Go ahead.
If you want to die so badly,
then challenge our Master.
It's your funeral.
He's so frightening, I
can't speak his name.
But here, let me try.
Gecko Mori.
Just as I thought.
It's too scary.
That's right!
He's one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea, you know?
Those missing friends of yours
are probably dead or even worse.
Consider yourself lucky
that you've lost so few.
I'd save my own skin if I were you.
If you face Gecko Merde...
I mean, if you face our master,
none of you will survive.
You'd do well to leave
before you incur his wrath.
Sorry, but I don't take
advice from paintings.
You want to help?
Give a message to that
stupid master of yours.
Tell him if he lays a single
finger on any of my friends,
I'll kick his ass so hard this
whole island will split in half.
Sanji's fine.
Even if he's alone, it's not like
he's just going to roll over and die.
Come on, guys.
Dear Master,
it would appear that
some rather terrifying
guests have made their way to your abode.
It is with no irony
that I say that they've
managed to surprise even
the surprise zombies.
Rise from your grave and raise your heart.
It's Fiesta time!
Bring those pirates to the ground.
Ride them and drag them through the grime.
And everyone is looking up.
Round and round until you die?
Samba!
Listen well.
The intruders have all
wandered into our territory.
They are our prey now.
Let your hunger run wild.
This will be a feast of terror!
Now awaken, zombie generals!
The fallen warriors shall
pick up their swords anew!
The Straw Hats are arrogant.
They number only eight.
They'll fall quickly.
Tear them down and offer
their bodies to our master!
Zombie generals, march forth and
teach them the meaning of fear!